Finding Aid for the Edward C. Weber Papers, 1949-2005
Edward C. Weber Papers
- Correspondence
  - Om (Amsterdam, Holland) (Box 34)
  - Omega (re: several anonymous donations) (Box 34)
  - On Target (Norborne, MO) (Box 34)
  - One, Inc. (Box 34)
  - One in Detroit (Box 34)
  - O’Neil, David (Box 34)
  - Onna (Tokyo) (Box 34)
  - Onubogu, Harold N. (Box 34)
  - Onward (Gainesville, FL) (Box 34)
  - Open Head Press ( Fanatic) (London, England) (Box 34)
  - Operation Bootstrap (Shreveport, LA) (Box 34)
  - Ophelia Editions (New York, NY) (Box 34)
  - Oppenheim, Lucy (re: job possibility in the LC) (Box 34)
  - Opus Gay (Lisbon, Portugal) (Box 34)
  - Oracle (Los Angeles, CA) (Box 34)
  - Orbach, Harold (re: donations to LC) (Box 34)
  - Orbis Publishing, Ltd. (reference: photographs for illustrated history of America) (Box 34)
  - Organization of Solidarity for the Peoples of Africa, Asia & Latin America (see O.S.P.A.A.A.L.) (Box 34)
  - Orpheus (Phoenix) (Box 34)
  - Orr, Charles A. (re: donations) (Box 34)
  - Orr, Laura (re: literary heir of Lois and Charles Orr) (Box 34)
  - Orth-Gutmann, Renate (reference: Robert Reitzel) (Box 34)
  - Orvis, Dellis (reference: John Orvis; Sovereigns of Industry) (Box 34)
  - O’Sullivan, Judith (reference: women in American labor) (Box 34)
  - Osborne, James (reference: Paterson, NJ strike of 1913; Italian anarchist movement of Paterson) (Box 34)
  - Other Countries: Black Gay Voices (New York)) (Box 34)
  - Other Scenes (New York, etc.) (Box 34)
  - Otter, Laurens (Box 34)
  - Our American Heritage Committee News Bulletin (Oklahoma City, OK) (Box 34)
  - Our Generation (Montréal, Quebec) (Box 34)
  - Outlines (Chicago) (Box 34)
  - Overthrow (New York) (Box 34)
  - Oz Magazine (London) (Box 34)
  - P., Phillip (Box 34)
  - P.A.R. Journal (People Against Racism) (Detroit) (Box 34)
  - P.E.T.A. (People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals) (Box 34)
  - P.O.S.R.I.P. (People Organized to Stop Rape of Imprisoned Persons) (Box 34)
  - Pacesetters (Philadelphia, PA) (Box 34)
  - Pacific Collective (M-L) (Berkeley, CA) (Box 34)
  - Pacific Historian (reference: Ralph Chaplin; Alexander Berkman) (Box 34)
  - Pacific Libertarian (Makiki, HI) (Box 34)
  - Pacific Street Production Corporation (reference: anarchists in NYC; radical gathering places in NYC) (Box 35)
  - Padilla, Raymond (reference: Mexican-American serials in the LC) (Box 35)
  - Paedophile Information Exchange (Kent, England) (Box 35)
  - Pa’fuera! (San Juan, Puerto Rico) (Box 35)
  - Page, Warren (3 folders) (Box 35)
  - Pagni, Charlotte (re: thank you to ECW for class presentation) (Box 35)
  - Paley, Richard P. (reference: Spanish Civil War) (Box 35)
  - Palmer, Ann (reference: Emma Goldman’s speeches) (Box 35)
  - Panarizon Publishing Corp. (reference: Joe Hill’s Rebel Girl sheet music) (Box 35)
  - Paolella, Edward C. (Box 35)
  - Park, James (re: his book offered to LC, Authentic Love: An Existential Vision) (Box 35)
  - Parker, Franklin (re: donation of his paper on Myles Horton for inclusion in LC) (Box 35)
  - Parker, S.E. (Sid) (letters dating from 1949-1998) (Box 35)
  - Parola del Popolo, La (Chicago, IL) (Box 35)
  - Parrish, Timothy C. (reference: Spanish Civil War; UGT; CNT; Riojo region) (Box 35)
  - Parry, Carl E. (donation of his Labor Legislation of Michigan, 1909 for inclusion in LC) (Box 35)
  - Partido Obrero Revolucionario ( Lucha Obrera) (La Paz, Bolivia) (Box 35)
  - Patch, Margaret (reference: Witchcraft in Uganda—article in Transition) (Box 35)
  - Pathfinder Press (New York) (Box 35)
  - Patino, Carlos (Box 35)
  - Patterson Museum (re: Edwin C. Walker’s literary executor) (Box 35)
  - Pawa, J. M. (reference: British IWW members imprisoned in Leavenworth) (Box 35)
  - Paxton, Evan (reference: Voltairine de Cleyre) (Box 35)
  - Payne, Kenneth (reference: Mike Gold; radical American literature of the 1930s) (Box 35)
  - Paz y Justica (Buenos Aires, Argentina) (Box 35)
  - Paz y Liberacion (Hollywood, CA; Houston, TX) (Box 35)
  - Peace & Freedom News (Berkeley, CA) (Box 35)
  - Peace Press (London) see International Confederation for Disarmament and Peace (Box 35)
  - Peace News (London) (Box 35)
  - Peacedom Digest (Chicago) (Box 35)
  - Pearlman, George (reference: first Labor Day in 1882; Central Labor Union; Machinists and (Box 35)
  - Blacksmiths Union; Thomas Wilson Talbot; Matthew Maguire) (Box 36)
  - Pearson, Mark (re: donation of libertarian materials) (Box 36)
  - Pedu, Richard K. (Box 36)
  - Peking Review (Peking, China) (Box 36)
  - Pennington, Jack G. (re: bibliography of radical literature) (Box 36)
  - People, The (Sydney, Australia) (Box 36)
  - People and Land (San Francisco, CA) (Box 36)
  - People’s Bicentennial Commission (Washington, DC) (Box 36)
  - People’s Bookseller (Tallahassee, FL) ( P.M. Newsletter) (Box 36)
  - People’s Press (San Francisco, CA) (Box 36)
  - People’s Tribune (Chicago, IL) (Communist Labor Party) (Box 36)
  - People’s Voice (Bellflower, CA) (CPUSA) (Box 36)
  - People’s World (San Francisco, CA) (Box 36)
  - Pereira, Raimundo (Box 36)
  - Perelli, John Jr. (reference: Emma Goldman’s life in Rochester, NY) (Box 36)
  - Perlman, Lorraine (Box 36)
  - Perlstein, Daniel (reference: Elizabeth Gurley Flynn) (Box 36)
  - Pernicone, Nunzio (reference: Carlo Tresca’s literary heir) (Box 36)
  - Peron, Jim (re: Christianity and homosexuality) (Box 36)
  - Perseus House, Inc. (Box 36)
  - Pesotta, Rose (from ECW, no reply) (Box 36)
  - Petal Paper, The (Fairhope, AL) (Box 36)
  - Petermann, Alfred G. (reference: Giessen Emigration Society; Karl Heinzen; German periodicals) (Box 36)
  - Peters, David (reference: Joseph Slight: Glassworkers) (Box 36)
  - Petersen, Peter L. (reference: Henry Vincent; Edwin and Thomas Meredith) (Box 36)
  - Peterson, Bendix (Box 36)
  - Peterson, Joyce (reference: Auto workers in non-union period) (Box 36)
  - Peterson, Karl (reference: John Dos Passos) (Box 36)
  - Petrick, Arthur (reference: Anthony Bimba; American Committee for the Protection of Foreign Born) (Box 36)
  - Phelps, Christopher (reference: Emanuel Kanter) (Box 36)
  - Phelps, James (reference: Benjamin Tucker) (Box 36)
  - Philadelphia Gay News (Box 36)
  - Philippines Research Center (Storrs, CT) (Box 36)
  - Phipps, Stanley G. (reference: labor history) (Box 36)
  - Phoenix News and Views (Phoenix Society) (Kansas City, MO) (Box 36)
  - Pianeta Fresco (Torino, Italy) (Box 36)
  - Piehl, Mel (reference: Catholic Worker; Ammon Hennacy) (Box 36)
  - Piehler, Harold (reference: Henry Vincent; Leopold Vincent; Populist movement in Kansas) (Box 36)
  - Pierce, Roy (re: transfer of French political surveys from ISR to LC) (Box 36)
  - Pierian Press (reference: genocide in Bangladesh) (Box 36)
  - Pilk, Inez (aka ECW) (Box 36)
  - Pink Triangle (Malaysia) (Box 36)
  - Pink Triangle (New Zealand) (Box 36)
  - Pink Triangle Press (Hong Kong) (Box 36)
  - Pinkham, Harold B. (to various employees in the LC) (Box 36)
  - Pinto, Vincent A. (reference: Lawrence textile strike of 1912) (Box 36)
  - Pintzuk, Edward C. (reference: Jewish trade unions in Detroit) (Box 36)
  - Plain Rapper (Palo Alto, CA) (Box 36)
  - Plain Truth, The (Champaign, IL) (Box 36)
  - Pl’Asada – Grupo Anarchico (Italy) (Box 36)
  - Poland, Jefferson (Box 36)
  - Polansky, Janet (reference: Helen Marot; Women’s Trade Union League) (Box 36)
  - Polenburg, Richard (reference: anarchism in the U.S. from 1912-1922) (Box 36)
  - Pollock, Mordeca Jane (reference: wants copy of First Essay on the Political Rights of Women) (Box 36)
  - Poor Richard’s Reports (Society of Separationists) (Austin, TX) (Box 36)
  - Pope, Daniel A. (reference: Emma Goldman; American anarchists) (Box 36)
  - Popeye (San Francisco) (Box 36)
  - Porpoise Press (Provincetown, MA) (Box 36)
  - Porter, David (reference: Spanish Civil War; Emma Goldman; literary heir) (Box 36)
  - Porter, Harold Irving (reference: assassination of John F. Kennedy) (Box 36)
  - Portuguese and Colonial Bulletin (London) (Box 36)
  - Pothen, Philip P. (Box 36)
  - Powell, Anton (re: sending copy of pamphlet, “Marked for Life” for inclusion in LC) (Box 36)
  - Powers, Lila (re: donation of Don Werkheiser Papers) (Box 36)
  - POZ Magazine (New York) (Box 36)
  - Practical Anarchy (Glasgow, Scotland) (Box 36)
  - Prairie Fire Distribution Committee (San Francisco) (Box 37)
  - Preece, Harold (reference: seeking copy of his article, “The Passion of Sacco and Vanzetti”) (Box 37)
  - Preston, John (re: author of The Big Gay Book; wants to include info on LC) (Box 37)
  - Price, Doug (re: purchase of photographs for LC) (Box 37)
  - Price, Isabel B. (reference: Gerald L.K. Smith) (Box 37)
  - Prickett, James (reference: American Communist Party and Communist front groups (Box 37)
  - Prikopa, John I (re: donation of his book) (Box 37)
  - Princeton University (reference: James Keir Hardie; death of Agnes Inglis) (Box 37)
  - Prison and Jail Project of North Carolina (Box 37)
  - Prisoners’ Union ( The Outlaw) (Box 37)
  - Programma Comunista, Il (Milano, Italy) (Box 37)
  - Progressive Labor (New York) (Box 37)
  - Progressive Workers Movement (Vancouver, BC) (Box 37)
  - Protesta, La (Argentina) (includes letters from Freedom Press) (Box 37)
  - Protos (Los Angeles, CA) (Box 37)
  - Prum, Michel (reference: John Francis Bray) (Box 37)
  - Psych-Agitator (Stony Brook, NY) (Box 37)
  - Pterodactyl (Grinnell, IA) (Box 37)
  - Public Affairs Press (reference: Socialist Party, IWW) (Box 37)
  - Puce Mongoose (Garwood, NJ) (Box 37)
  - Pudup, Mary Beth (reference: Ku Klux Klan during Reconstruction) (Box 37)
  - Puebla Institute (New York) (Box 37)
  - Punto Crítico (Zacatecas, Mexico) (Box 37)
  - Purdue University Library (reference: seeking bibliographies on homosexuality for acquisition) (Box 37)
  - Purdy/Kresge Library, Wayne State University (re: ECW to borrow André Gill materials for exhibit) (Box 37)
  - Pushpin, Lubalin & Peckolick (reference: images of pacifism and anti-war movements) (Box 37)
  - Pyrmid Periodical (New York, NY) (Box 37)
  - Quam-Wichham, Nancy (reference: California oil workers; IWW; Socialist Party) (Box 37)
  - Quartich, Bernard (re: Dachine Rainer papers) (Box 37)
  - Qué Hacer? (Costa Rica) (Box 37)
  - Quest: a feminist quarterly (Washington DC) (Box 37)
  - Quarterly Intercsange (San Francisco, CA) (Box 37)
  - RFD (Iowa; Tennessee) (Box 37)
  - Race Relations Information Center ( Race Relations Report) (Nashville, TN) (Box 37)
  - Radical Education (London, England) (Box 37)
  - Radical Education Project (Detroit, MI) (Box 37)
  - Radical Historians Caucus (Somerville, MA) (Box 37)
  - Radical History Review (New York) (Box 37)
  - Radical Individualist (Portland, OR) (Box 37)
  - Radical Religion (Berkeley, CA) (Box 37)
  - Radio Free People (New York) (Box 37)
  - Radosh, Ronald (letters from ECW) (Box 37)
  - Rafferty, Edward (reference: Lester Frank Ward) (Box 37)
  - Rag, The (Austin, TX) (Box 37)
  - Rahman, Ajile A. (reference: Muhammed Speaks) (Box 37)
  - Rainer, Dachine (Box 37)
  - Rally Magazine (Wauwatosa, WI) (Box 37)
  - Ramer, Richard (book dealer) (Box 37)
  - Rampart College Newsletter (Santa Ana, CA) (Box 37)
  - Ramparts Magazine (Berkeley, CA) (Box 37)
  - Ramsey, Cheryl Y. (Box 37)
  - Ramsey, Ronald (reference: Honoré Joseph Jaxon) (Box 37)
  - Ramsey, Jerold (reference: Redpath’s Weekly) (Box 37)
  - Rand Corporation (reference: The Alternative Press) (Box 37)
  - Randolph, A. Philip (re: The Messenger) (Box 37)
  - Random House (reference: photograph of Margaret Sanger for The American Century textbook) (Box 37)
  - Rank and File (London, England) (Box 37)
  - Rappaport, Philip (reference: pictorial history of working women in America) (Box 37)
  - Rapport, Beatrice (daughter of Carlo Tresca) (Box 37)
  - Rasmussen, Bill (Box 37)
  - Rat, The (New York) (Box 37)
  - Rational Individualist (Silver Spring, MD) (Box 37)
  - Raza, La (Los Angeles, CA) (Box 37)
  - Reade, Maxwell (Box 37)
  - Reader’s Digest (reference: Joe Hill sheet music for American Folklore and Legend) (Box 37)
  - Realist (San Francisco, CA) (Box 38)
  - Reason (re: letter from ECW regarding None Dare Call It Treason/Reason) (Box 38)
  - Rebel Voices (New York) – file not in box (Box 38)
  - Rebellion News (Roxbury, MA) (Box 38)
  - Recht Voor Allen (Amsterdam, Holland) (Box 38)
  - Recon Publications (Box 38)
  - Reconstruir (Buenos Aires, Argentina) (Box 38)
  - Red Balloon (Port Jefferson, NY) (Box 38)
  - Red Books (London, England) (Box 38)
  - Red House Books (San Francisco, CA) (Box 38)
  - Red Lion Press (Montréal, Quebec) (Box 38)
  - Red Menace (Toronto, Ontario) (Box 38)
  - Red Mole (London, England) (Box 38)
  - Red Notes (London, England) (Box 38)
  - Red Papers (San Francisco, CA) (Box 38)
  - Red Times (Detroit, MI) (Box 38)
  - Redding, R.W. (reference: Ralph Chaplin) (Box 38)
  - Reddy, Enver (Box 38)
  - Redfern, Walter (reference: Georges Darien; L’Ennemi du Peuple; etc.) (Box 38)
  - Rediker, Marcus (reference: Alexander Berkman; Johann Most) (Box 38)
  - Reed, Theodore L. (donation of materials relating to SDS and SLID) (Box 38)
  - Reeve, Carl (reference: James Connolly) (Box 38)
  - Reflections the Free South Review (Chapel Hill, NC) (Box 38)
  - Réfractaire (Le Pré Saint Gervais, France) (Box 38)
  - Regeneración, (Mexico) (Box 38)
  - Regeneración (Los Angeles, CA) (Box 38)
  - Reich, Eva (re: donation of Wilhelm Reich microfilms) (Box 38)
  - Reichard, Richard (reference: Nordstern) (Box 38)
  - Reichert, William O. (reference: Josiah Warren; American anarchism) (Box 38)
  - Reid, Thomas (reference: history of Trotskyism in North American to 1960) (Box 38)
  - Reid-Farr, Robert F. (letter from ECW) (Box 38)
  - Reintjes, Monique (reference: Odette Keun) (Box 38)
  - Reinsdorf, Walter D. (reference: wants microfilm of Freiheit) (Box 38)
  - Reiser, Robert S. (reference: photos for book about working people in the U.S.) (Box 38)
  - Reisman, Gail (reference: Emma Goldman material on microfilm) (Box 38)
  - Reiss, Ansgar (reference: Gustav (von) Struve) (Box 38)
  - Reitz, Thomas (re: Leon Kramer Collection at UW-Green Bay) (Box 38)
  - Relgis, Eugen (Box 38)
  - Rene Guyon Society (Box 38)
  - Renegade, The (Tacoma, WA) (Box 38)
  - Renshaw, Patrick (reference: IWW) (Box 38)
  - Research Foundation for Jewish Immigration (reference: German-speaking refugees from Nazism) (Box 38)
  - Resist Newsletter (Cambridge, MA) (Box 38)
  - Resistance (New York) (letter from David Weick) (Box 38)
  - Resistance Publications ( Chilean Resistance Courier) (Oakland, CA) (Box 38)
  - Resistenza (Torino, Italy) (Box 38)
  - Resource Center for Philippine Concerns (Hong Kong) (Box 38)
  - Respond (Boston, MA) (Box 38)
  - Retherford, Sylvia E. (reference: Lois Waisbrooker) (Box 38)
  - Rethinking Marxism (Northampton, MA) (Box 38)
  - Retzloff, Tim (Box 38)
  - Reuben, William (re: donation of papers) (Box 38)
  - Reuther Library (re: ECW article in Labor History) (Box 38)
  - Review of Radical Political Economics (Ann Arbor, MI) (Box 38)
  - Review of the News (Belmont, MA) (Box 38)
  - Revisionist Press, The (re: Laurance Labadie’s writing for publication) (Box 38)
  - Revista Acracia (Costa Rica) (Box 38)
  - Revolt (Sweden?) (seized by U.S. Customs on charges of obscenity) (Box 38)
  - Revolution (Chicago, IL) (RCP) (Box 38)
  - Revolution Socialiste (Martinique, West Indies) (Box 38)
  - Revolutionary Age (Seattle) (Box 38)
  - Revolutionary Autoworkers Committee (Detroit, MI) (Box 38)
  - Revolutionary People’s Communication Network (New York) (Box 38)
  - Revolutionary Union (San Francisco, CA) (Box 38)
  - Revolutionary Workers Congress (Detroit, MI) (Box 38)
  - Revolutionary Workers Party (Red Flag) (London, England) (Box 38)
  - Reynolds, Paul (re: donation of anarchist materials from former SRAF member) (Box 38)
  - Rhodes, James B. (reference: Socialist Party presidential campaign of 1920) (Box 38)
  - Ribuffo, Leo P. (reference: Gerald L.K. Smith) (Box 38)
  - Ricci, James (re: article on Sunrise Community in Detroit Free Press) (Box 38)
  - Rice, Warner (re: death of Mary Rice) (Box 38)
  - Rich, Janet (reference: hidden history and culture of gay women and men) (Box 38)
  - Richardson, Ronald – wasn’t on finding aid (Box 38)
  - Richter, John Henry (re: microfilming Readers Speak Out!) (Box 38)
  - Riché, Nicole Tucker (re: literary rights of Benjamin Tucker) (Box 38)
  - Richter, John Henry (re: Du Bois, Aptheker, Hugo Rolland, Comunita) (Box 38)
  - Rickman, Ray (reference: Justice Marshall) (Box 38)
  - Riddle, Dave (reference: Warren Tank Plant march of April 1971) (Box 38)
  - Rodinger, Robert (reference: microfilming of gay newspapers) (Box 38)
  - Right to Work Campaign (London, England) (Box 38)
  - Riley, Monica (reference: Nation of Islam) (Box 38)
  - Rimmer, Robert (re: The Harrad Experiment) (Box 38)
  - Rinehart, Blanche (reference: Philip Taft; International Typographical Union of Detroit; Gompers) (Box 38)
  - Rischin, Moses (reference: Abraham Cahan) (Box 38)
  - Rising Up Angry (Chicago) (Box 38)
  - Ritchie, Gladys (reference: Port Huron Statement; Tom Hayden; SDS; rhetoric of student protest) (Box 38)
  - Ritter, Gretchen (reference: antimonopolism; Greenbacks; IWW; Knights of Labor, etc.) (Box 38)
  - Rivera, Bob (reference: copies of IWW Walsh-Lahr photos; IWW; E.G. Flynn; Palmer Raids, etc.) (Box 39)
  - Robb, Pauline Forman (re: Sunrise Community donation) (Box 39)
  - Robert F. Williams Tribute Committee (letter from ECW-no response-returned) (Box 39)
  - Roberts, Joe (reference: anti-revisionist communist movement in U.S. from 1940s to 1970s) (Box 39)
  - Roberts, John (re: donation of New Left materials) (Box 39)
  - Robertson, Martha (Box 39)
  - Robie, Carroll H. (re: donation of human sexuality books by Walter Robie) (Box 39)
  - Robilotta, Peter (reference: Ralph Chaplin autograph book) (Box 39)
  - Robinson, Cedric (reference: Abraham Lincoln Brigade; role of Blacks in the Spanish Civil War) (Box 39)
  - Robinson, Jo Ann O. (reference: A.J. Muste) (Box 39)
  - Rochester, N.Y., Public Library (re: Stella Cominsky Ballantine) (Box 39)
  - Rock, Allan L. (re: donation of his papers, personal matters) (Box 39)
  - Rock and Roll Hall of Fame (Box 39)
  - Rodger Friedman Antiquarian Books (Box 39)
  - Rodgers, Curtis and Clarice (1 - 11 of 18 folders) (Box 39)
  - Rodgers, Curtis and Clarice (12 - 18 of 18 folders) (Box 40)
  - Rodrigo, Antonina (re: donation of books) (Box 40)
  - Rodriguez, Oriente Neber Diaz (re: gay movement in Uruguay) (Box 40)
  - Roediger, Dave (reference: Covington Hall; John Nicholas Beffel) (Box 40)
  - Roewer, Edward W. (re: great grandson of Karl Heinzen) (Box 40)
  - Rogow, Zack (re: donation of anarchist materials—Bookchin; Anarchos) (Box 40)
  - Rolies, Jan (reference: Iwan Block) (Box 40)
  - Rolland, Hugo (re: donation of Italian anarchist materials) (Box 40)
  - Rolland, Siphra (re: donation of husband Hugo Rolland’s materials) (Box 40)
  - Rollman, Mary (Box 40)
  - Romano, Rene (reference: black-white interracial marriage in the U.S. from 1945-1990; Club of Tomorrow in Detroit) (Box 40)
  - Romberg, Bill (reference: music about Milwaukee; G. Vail Williams; R.W. Wooby) (Box 40)
  - Romer, James H. (reference: bibliography of current left movements) (Box 40)
  - Rooks, Marjorie (Putnam) (reference: The Story of New Harmony) (Box 40)
  - Rooks, John and Marjorie (Box 40)
  - Rooks, JC (Box 40)
  - Roosevelt, James (Box 40)
  - Root & Branch (Somerville, MA) (Box 40)
  - Roots (New York) (Box 40)
  - Roper, William L. (reference: Joe Hill; James O. Morris) (Box 40)
  - Rosary College (re: From Radical Left to Extreme Right) (Box 40)
  - Rosalik, Bernard (re: donation of WWI Polish posters) (Box 40)
  - Roseman, Herbert C. (re: donation of Laurance Labadie books belonging to Roseman) (Box 40)
  - Rosemont, Henry (reference: David Boyd’ The Labor Movement of Detroit) (Box 40)
  - Rosemont, Franklin (reference: various anarchist and IWW questions) (Box 40)
  - Rosen, Nancy (reference: photographs of Olivia and Helen Rossetti) (Box 40)
  - Rosenberg, Marc (re: donation of SDS scrapbook of Queens College Chapter) (Box 40)
  - Rosenberg, Mark (re: Amalgamation Party; The Printing Worker) (Box 40)
  - Rosenblum, Henry (reference: Individualist anarchists; Minus One) (Box 40)
  - Rosenthal, Anton (reference: history of anarchism and IWW in Latin America) (Box 40)
  - Rosenthall, Susan A. (re: donation of The Radical Therapist; Rough Times; Issues in Radical Therapy) (Box 40)
  - Rosenzweig, Roy (reference: unemployed organizations in Britain and U.S. in 1930s) (Box 40)
  - Rosini, Vincent (reference: Orrin Giddings Cocks; National Committee for Better Films) (Box 40)
  - Ross, Greg (Box 40)
  - Ross, Marc (reference: Peter J. McGuire) (Box 40)
  - Rossi, Bob (re: American Federation of Miners; offer to sell his books) (Box 40)
  - Rossman, Michael (re: political posters; AOUON Archive) (Box 40)
  - Rosswurm, Kevin (reference: IWW strike in Akron, OH, 1913) (Box 40)
  - Rosswurm, Steven (reference: general info) (Box 40)
  - Rostenberg and Stern Rare Books (Box 40)
  - Roth, Robert (reference: project to microfilm all LGBT materials for NGTF) (Box 40)
  - Roth, Susan (reference: American radical and underground newspapers) (Box 40)
  - Rotstein, Andrew (reference: October League) (Box 40)
  - Roy, Nena (Box 40)
  - Rudenko-Rudolph, Hryhorij Nestor (reference: donation of manuscript on anarchist history) (Box 40)
  - Rudolph, Jim and A. (Box 40)
  - Ruge, Valice (re: donation of Arnold Ruge papers) (Box 40)
  - Ruja, Harry (reference: Bertrand Russell bibliography) (Box 40)
  - Rush, E.L. (Box 40)
  - Russell, Francis (reference: letter from Vanzetti to Rose Pesotta, 1927) (Box 41)
  - Russell, Robert R. (reference: donation of his letters to the editor) (Box 41)
  - Russo, Johnny (re: offer to send Antikrat; in prison for bombings) (Box 41)
  - Ruta (Caracas, Venezuela) (Box 41)
  - Rutledge, Leigh W. (Box 41)
  - S.O.S.!!!, U.S.A., Ship of State (Salem, MA) (Box 41)
  - SRAFprint Co-op (Social Revolutionary Anarchist Federation) (Box 41)
  - St. Francis of Assisi House (re: publications on Catholic radicalism) (Box 41)
  - Saint Amour, Michele (Box 41)
  - Saint Laurent, Ronald (reference: anarchists in the Portuguese Revolution of 1974-75) (Box 41)
  - Sabatini, Peter (reference: marginalization of anarchism after 1900) (Box 41)
  - Saenz, Gil (re: donation of his book of poetry) (Box 41)
  - Salem, Dorothy (reference: photograph of Lucy Parsons) (Box 41)
  - Salemme, Antonio (re: sent photographs of Paul Robeson statue) (Box 41)
  - Salerno, Salvatore (reference: anarchist influences in the IWW; Irving Abrams; Thomas Hagerty) (Box 41)
  - Salted Feathers (Portland, OR) (Box 41)
  - Salter, John R. (re: donation of his articles on Ralph Chaplin, Mississippi, etc.) (Box 41)
  - Samizdat Bulletin (San Mateo, CA) (Box 41)
  - Samoff, Joel (re: inaccessibility of LC materials with long reply from Anne Okey) (Box 41)
  - Samuel Gompers Papers, The (reference: want copies of all Gompers letter in LC) (Box 41)
  - San Diego’s Daily Impulse (Box 41)
  - San Francisco African-American Historical & Cultural Society (formerly S.F. Negro etc.) (Box 41)
  - San Francisco Ball (Box 41)
  - San Francisco Bay Area Gay & Lesbian Historical Society (Box 41)
  - San Francisco Mime Troupe (Box 41)
  - San Francisco Public Library (Box 41)
  - Sandos, James A. (reference: William C. Owen) (Box 41)
  - SANE World (Washington DC) (Box 41)
  - Sanger, Alexander C. (reference: Margaret Sanger) (Box 41)
  - Sanity (Montreal, Québec) (Box 41)
  - Sannes, Erling (reference: Knights of Labor in the Dakota Territory; George Schilling) (Box 41)
  - SantaVicca, Edmund F. (re: donation of bibliography on sexual minorities) (Box 41)
  - Sappho (London, England) (Box 41)